{
    "subject": "resource/Roger_O'Donnell",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1955",
    "human_readable": "Roger O'Donnell was born in 1955.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.900439977645874,
            "question": "In what year was Roger O'Donnell born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8397043943405151,
            "question": "Where was Roger O'Donnell born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5382183790206909,
            "question": "What is Roger O'Donnell known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.388864666223526,
            "question": "Which band was Roger O'Donnell a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.314762145280838,
            "question": "What were some of Roger O'Donnell's notable musical contributions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2686794400215149,
            "question": "Has Roger O'Donnell collaborated with other artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26227906346321106,
            "question": "Is Roger O'Donnell still active in the music industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22058410942554474,
            "question": "What genre of music is Roger O'Donnell associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18890197575092316,
            "question": "What musical instrument does Roger O'Donnell play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16980908811092377,
            "question": "What is the name of Roger O'Donnell's solo album?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Roger O'Donnell was born in 1955.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2604_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical instrument does Roger O'Donnell play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2604_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is Roger O'Donnell associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2604_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Roger O'Donnell still active in the music industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2604_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2604_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2604_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2604_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2604_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2604_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2604_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2604_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2604_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2604_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2604_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references stating that Roger O'Donnell was born on October 29, 1955."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}